<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Nusantara Travel</string>
    <string name="Title">Bali</string>
    <string name="Title2">Bandung</string>
    <string name="Title3">Bogor</string>
    <string name="Role1">Hotel-Restaurant</string>
    <string name="Role2">Hotel-Restaurant</string>
    <string name="Role3">Home Stay-Restaurant-Caffe</string>
    <string name="imagehal1">ImageHal1</string>
    <string name="Titlesub1">Tanah Lot</string>
    <string name="Titlesub1_2">Kuta Beach</string>
    <string name="Titlesub1_3">Pusa Ulun Lake</string>
    <string name="Titlesub1_4">Bebek Betutu</string>
    <string name="TitleSubBio">Bio</string>
    <string name="TitleView">Place View</string>
    <string name="TitleSubEnd">Recommended</string>
    <string name="Desc1">Tanah Lot if translated into Indonesian means land in the middle of the sea. Tanah means land, Lot means sea.</string>
    <string name="Desc2">"Kuta beach attractions will always be included in the list of tourist attractions to visit on the island of Bali for tourists who have their first vacation to Bali. The main thing that makes Kuta beach crowded with tourist visits because it offers a long stretch of white sand beach and sunset views. "</string>
    <string name="Desc3">"Ulun Danu Temple which is located on the edge of Lake Beratan in the tourist area of ​​Bedugul. According to Wikipedia, the location of Lake Beratan Bedugul is at an altitude of 1,200 meters above sea level. Therefore, the air around the Ulun Danu Beratan Temple area is very cool. "</string>
    <string name="DescBio">"bali is a province in Indonesia whose provincial capital is Denpasar. Bali is also one of the islands in the Nusa Tenggara Islands. At the beginning of Indonesia's independence, the island was included in the Lesser Sunda Province, which has a capital city in Singaraja, and is now divided into 3 provinces: Bali, West Nusa Tenggara and East Nusa Tenggara. "</string>
    <string name="Desc4">"Bebek Betutu is a very popular Balinese food. If you hear the word Bali, you will definitely remember this traditional Balinese food. The cooking process is quite long. Before cooking, the duck will be seasoned and then given a massage so that the spices absorb perfectly. In addition, the meat will be more tender and tender. Then the ducks are wrapped in areca leaves or banana leaves. Cook it by baking in the husk for a long time. Bebek Betutu is always served during religious ceremonies or other traditional events. For those of you who don't like duck meat, you can try Betutu Chicken. One of the places to cook duck Betutu is in the village of Melinggih, Payangan sub-district, Gianyar regency. "</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="kapal">Ship</string>
    <string name="Kereta">Train</string>
    <string name="pesawat">Air Plan</string>
    <string name="title_trans">Transportation Available</string>
    <string name="Titlesub2_1">Kawah Putih</string>
    <string name="Titlesub2_2">Grafika Cikole</string>
    <string name="Titlesub2_3">Tebing Kraton</string>
    <string name="Titlesub2_4">Bandros</string>
    <string name="Desc2_1">"The beauty of this spectacular sight can make anyone hypnotized. This crater will sometimes turn milky brown and more often white when the air is filled with an invulnerable fog. "</string>
    <string name="Desc2_2">"Grafika Cikole is a tourist location in the form of inns and restaurants which are very suitable to be used as a vacation spot with family. The location which is surrounded by pine forests has an area of ​​9 hectares and has a very cool air. Apart from doing outbound activities, you can also do many interesting activities. For example picking strawberries, playing in a tree house, flying fox, camping to pre-wedding. "</string>
    <string name="Desc2_3">This tourist spot presents a very spectacular natural scenery and is visited by many tourists. Lots of visitors who deliberately come to just take hits with the background of the expanse of the forest park and the fresh air. You can also see the rows of hills that appear to be towering from a distance, so that everyone who visits will feel calm when seeing this view.</string>
    <string name="Desc2_4">Bandros One of Bandung\'s most popular traditional snacks is bandros. This cake made from a mixture of rice flour and coconut milk is shaped like a pukis with a savory taste. There is a sprinkling of sugar to add flavor.</string>
    <string name="DescBio2">"Bandung is the largest metropolitan city in West Java Province, as well as the capital of the province. ota kembang is another name for this city, because in ancient times this city was considered very beautiful with many trees and flowers growing there. In addition, Bandung was formerly known as Parijs van Java because of its beauty. In addition, the city of Bandung is also known as a shopping city, with malls and factory outlets that are widely scattered in this city, and now Bandung is gradually becoming a city for culinary tourism. "</string>
    <string name="Titlesub3_1">Telaga Saat</string>
    <string name="Titlesub3_2">Curug Cikuluwung</string>
    <string name="Titlesub3_3">Gunung Pancar</string>
    <string name="Titlesub3_4">Cungkring Bogor</string>
    <string name="Desc3_1">" One of the newest tourist spots in the Bogor Puncak area is a lake hidden between tea plantations. The name of this newest tourist spot in Bogor is Telaga Saat."</string>
    <string name="Desc3_2">A famous natural tourist spot in Pangandaran. Well, this waterfall has the nickname Little Green Canyon because of its similarity to the body rafting tourist spot, only this is the mini version.</string>
    <string name="Desc3_3">For nature lovers, this tourist attraction around Bogor and Puncak can be the right refreshing alternative. The charm of pine forests in this tourist area is popular as a place to shoot camera lenses and also as a favorite pre-wedding photo location.</string>
    <string name="Desc3_4">Bogor\'s next specialty food is cungkring. This food has a unique name like the name for people who are too thin but this food is not the case.</string>
    <string name="DescBio3">Bogor\'s next specialty food is cungkring. This food has a unique name like the name for people who are too thin but this food is not the case.</string>
    <string name="Title4">Semarang</string>
    <string name="Title6">Padang</string>
    <string name="Title5">Jogja</string>
    <string name="Title7">Surabaya</string>
    <string name="Title8">Batu Jawatimur</string>
    <string name="Title9">Lombok</string>
    <string name="Title10">Jakarta</string>
    <string name="Titlesub4_1">Kota lama</string>
    <string name="Titlesub4_2">Benteng Pandem</string>
    <string name="Titlesub4_3">Taman Wilis</string>
    <string name="Titlesub4_4">Mie Kopyok</string>
    <string name="Bio4">"Semarang City is the capital city of Central Java Province, Indonesia as well as the fifth largest metropolitan city in Indonesia after Jakarta, Surabaya, Medan and Bandung. As one of the most developed cities on the island of Java, Semarang City has a population of more than 1.7 million people and during the day can reach 2 million inhabitants. The mega-urban area of ​​Semarang, which is part of the Kedungsepur metropolitan area (Kendal, Demak, Ungaran, Semarang Regency, Salatiga City, Semarang City and Purwodadi, Grobogan Regency) has a population of 7.3 million, as well as the fourth most populous metropolitan area, after Jabodetabek ( Jakarta), Gerbangkertosusilo (Surabaya), and Bandung Raya. "</string>
    <string name="Desc4_1">"Old City Traces of colonial heritage in Semarang can be found in the Kota Lama area, which is located on Jalan Letjen Suprapto, Tanjung Mas, North Semarang District, Semarang City. Visiting the Old City feels like abroad. The buildings there are built with European nuances which are suitable as photo locations. "</string>
    <string name="Desc4_2">"Ambarawa Benteng Pandem or Fort Fort Willem I is an old Dutch heritage building. This place is perfect for photo backgrounds. This fortress with instagramable Dutch architecture is located in Bugisari, Lodoyong, Ambarawa District, Semarang Regency. "</string>
    <string name="Desc4_3">"Beautiful scenery and cool air are presented in Wilis Park, which is located at Jalan Wilis number 3, Tegalsari, Candisari District, Semarang City. "</string>
    <string name="Desc4_4">"Mie kopyok is one of the tastiest foods in Semarang. Kopyok noodles themselves are made with the main ingredient of noodles which are added with meat drops and several other side dishes. One thing that makes kopyok noodles different is the addition of gendar crackers, which are a type of cracker made from very tasty and crunchy rice dough. "</string>
    <string name="Titlesub5_1">Tugu Jogja</string>
    <string name="Titlesub5_2">Candi Ratu Boko</string>
    <string name="Titlesub5_3">Kalibiru</string>
    <string name="Titlesub5_4">Sate Klatak</string>
    <string name="Desc5_1">"Tugu Pal Putih is another name for Tugu Jogja which contains a lot of meaning and philosophy in the monument. The location of Tugu Jogja is on Jenderal Sudirman and Margo Utama streets, which are located at a crossroads that are symbolic of Jogja. "</string>
    <string name="Desc5_2">Ratu Boko Temple or actually known as the royal complex is located on a high hill in the village of Bokoharjo, which is about 195.97 meters above sea level. The iconic entrance gate, the beautiful and wide expanse of grass, paseban, cave, the former pavilion, and the princess with a very unique pool will spoil your eyes.</string>
    <string name="Desc5_3">Kalibiru Nature Tourism is located on the western side of the Yogyakarta Special Region, namely in Kulon Progo which is very popular with tourists from various regions. The route to this tourist attraction in Kalibiru is not difficult and the terrain is easy to reach, especially if you pass the Sermo Reservoir which has a beautiful panorama.</string>
    <string name="Desc5_4">Sate Klatak is included in the list of the most delicious Jogjakarta specialties and must be tried. The uniqueness of this Sate Klatak is a piece of young mutton that is pierced using bars, different from other satay. The seasoning used is slightly different from regular goat satay, and is usually added with a sprinkling of appetizing curry sauce.</string>
    <string name="DescBio5">"Yogyakarta Special Region is located in the southern part of Java Island, and borders the Province of Central Java and the Indian Ocean. This Special Region which has an area of ​​3,185.80 km2 consists of one city and four districts, which are further divided into 78 Kapanewon / Kemantren and 438 Kelurahan / Kelurahan. "</string>
    <string name="DescBio6">"The city of Padang is the largest city on the west coast of Sumatra Island and the capital of the province of West Sumatra, Indonesia. This city is Indonesia's western gateway from the Indian Ocean. [5] Geographically, Padang is hilly with an altitude of 1,853 masl with an area of ​​694.96 km², of which more than half is protected forest. Based on data from the Central Statistics Agency (BPS) in 2017, this city has a population of 927,168 people. Padang is the core city of the development of the Palapa metropolitan area. "</string>
    <string name="Titlesub6_1">Pulau Sikuai</string>
    <string name="Desc6_1">"Sikuai Island is one of the first destinations you can visit. Sikuai Island has a beautiful and natural natural beauty that will make the atmosphere comfortable and calm. This island is visited by many tourists who already have a partner or tourists who want to honeymoon. "</string>
    <string name="Titlesub6_2">Pulau Nirwana</string>
    <string name="Desc6_2">The next natural tourist destination is Nirwana Beach. This beach is visited by many tourists, especially on weekends and summer holidays. Nirwana Beach presents beautiful natural scenery coupled with a refreshing breeze.</string>
    <string name="Titlesub6_3">Air Terjun Tingkat</string>
    <string name="Desc6_3">Untuk wisatawan yang hobi menjelajah alam, datang ke Air Terjun Tiga Tingkat merupakan salah satu pilihan yang tepat untuk dilakukan. Walaupun letak air terjun ini yang belum begitu terkenal di kalangan masyarakat, namun pesona alam yang ada di dalamnya sangat menawan.</string>
    <string name="Titlesub6_4">Rendang</string>
    <string name="Desc6_4">This traditional Padang culinary has been named the most delicious food in the world by CNN. The delicacy of beef cooked with a mixture of herbs and spices is certainly delicious.</string>
    <string name="DescBio7">"Surabaya is the capital city of East Java Province, Indonesia, as well as the largest metropolitan city in the province. Surabaya is also the second largest city in Indonesia after Jakarta. The city is located 800 km east of Jakarta, or 435 km northwest of Denpasar, Bali. Surabaya is located on the north coast of the eastern part of Java Island and faces the Madura Strait and the Java Sea. "</string>
    <string name="Titlesub7_1">Ekowisata Mangrove</string>
    <string name="Desc7_1">Mangrove Ecotourism which is located on Jalan Raya Wonorejo number 1, Rungkut District. This tourist spot is so popular with tourists because they can feel the green area in the middle of the hot Surabaya weather.</string>
    <string name="Titlesub7_2">Monument Kapal Selam</string>
    <string name="Desc7_2">"The next cool place you can visit in the city of Surabaya is the Submarine Monument. This monument is located at Jalan Pemuda Number 39 in the Genteng area. In this place you can see live various military vehicles on display. "</string>
    <string name="Titlesub7_3">Hutan Bamboo Putih</string>
    <string name="Desc7_3">Keputih Bamboo Forest which is on Jalan Raya Marina Asri, Keputih area, Sukolilo. In the past, this place was just a garbage dump which was later transformed into a beautiful and beautiful natural tourism. With a charming Sakura flower garden, tourists always come to this place.</string>
    <string name="Titlesub7_4">Rujak Cingur</string>
    <string name="Desc7_4">For those of you who claim to be a rujak lover, you must try this one salad. Cingur salad consists of two types, namely rujak cingur matengan which all the ingredients are cooked and rujak cingur mixed with fruit. In cingur matengan salad there are side dishes of lontong, bean sprouts, kale, fried tofu, fried tempeh and cingur. As for the mixed fruit salad cingur, it will add pineapple, young mango, yam and cucumber. This typical Surabaya food is very famous and delicious.</string>
    <string name="DescBio8">Kota Batu is a city in the province of East Java, Indonesia. The city is located 90 km southwest of Surabaya or 15 km northwest of Malang. Batu City is on the route connecting Malang-Kediri and Malang-Jombang. Batu City is bordered by Mojokerto Regency and Pasuruan Regency in the north and Malang Regency in the east, south, and west. The city area is located at an altitude of 700-2,000 meters and an average altitude of 871 meters [4] above sea level with an average temperature of 11-19 degrees Celsius.</string>
    <string name="Titlesub8_1">Jatim Park</string>
    <string name="Desc8_1">Starting from a relatively new tour, namely Jatim Park 3. This tourist spot made by Jatim Park Group, was only officially opened in 2017. By taking the theme of a dinosaur park for the main spot. In Dino Park, you will be transported to an era where there are still dinosaurs. This park is equipped with a Dino Park area with Middle Eastern nuances, Ice Age, and many others.</string>
    <string name="Titlesub8_2">Batu Night Spectacular</string>
    <string name="Desc8_2">One of the tourist attractions that are also members of the Jatim Park Group, namely Batu Night Spectacular. This tour, offers a different sensation from the others. You can ride rides, accompanied by the cool air of Batu City at night.</string>
    <string name="Titlesub8_3">Museum Angkut</string>
    <string name="Desc8_3">Still under the auspices of the East Java Group, there is another educational tour located in Batu Malang, namely the Angkut Museum. This museum has more than 300 collections of classic cars and motorbikes around the world.</string>
    <string name="Titlesub8_4">Sate Landak</string>
    <string name="Desc8_4">This satay has a soft texture and has a savory taste. One of the places to taste the famous hedgehog satay is Bu Ria\'s Warung Sate Landak, located at alan Raya Bugis 47, Saptorenggo, Pakis, Malang. Not only satay, you can also find food from other hedgehogs such as tongseng and rica-rica.</string>
    <string name="Titlesub9_1">Gunung Rinjani</string>
    <string name="Desc9_1">In an area of ​​about 40,000 hectares, stands the second highest volcano in Indonesia, namely Mount Rinjani. There are two official hiking routes to reach the mountain with an altitude of 3,762 meters above sea level. You can choose the Senaru line in North Lombok or Sembalun in East Lombok.</string>
    <string name="Titlesub9_2">Sagara Anak</string>
    <string name="Desc9_2">The name Segara Anak must be familiar, especially for climbers of Mount Rinjani. This place is a favorite of tourists who want to spend the night while hiking. This volcanic lake with a depth of 230 meters, was once a former volcanic crater which was then flooded, turning into a lake.\\</string>
    <string name="Titlesub9_3">Bukit Pergasingan</string>
    <string name="Desc9_3">One of the best spots to admire the splendor of Rinjani without having to climb to the top is at Pergasingan Hill. The hill to the east of Rinjani is increasingly popular among climbers and tourists. Pergasingan Hill is located in Sembalun, East Lombok.</string>
    <string name="Titlesub9_4">Ares</string>
    <string name="Desc9_4">Don\'t worry, this is not the name of the God of War from Greek mythology. On the other hand, this authentic Lombok food is cooked using the basic ingredients of banana leaves plus coconut milk. Usually served in conjunction with the wedding ceremony of the Sasak Tribe. Fortunately, now travelers can eat Ares at any time. There are already a number of restaurants in Lombok that offer this menu. Just like Plecing Kangkung, Ares will taste more delicious when eaten with white rice.</string>
    <string name="DescBio9">The island of Lombok (total population in 2001: 2,722,123 people) [1] is an island in the Lesser Sunda Islands or Nusa Tenggara which is separated by the Lombok Strait from Bali to the west and the Alas Strait to the east from Sumbawa. The island is roughly round in shape with a kind of \"tail\" on the southwest side which is approximately 70 km long. The area of ​​the island reaches 5,435 km² placing it in the 108th rank of the list of islands based on its size in the world. The main city on the island is Mataram City.</string>
    <string name="DescBio10">The Special Capital Region of Jakarta (DKI Jakarta) is the national capital and the largest city in Indonesia. Jakarta is the only city in Indonesia that has provincial-level status. Jakarta is located on the northwest coast of Java Island. In the past, several names were known, including Sunda Kelapa, Jayakarta, and Batavia. Internationally, Jakarta also has the nickname J-Town, [9] or more popularly The Big Durian because it is considered a city that is comparable to New York City (Big Apple) in Indonesia.</string>
    <string name="Titlesub10_1">Kepulauan Seribu</string>
    <string name="Desc10_1">The capital city of Jakarta also has beautiful marine tourism spots that are no less than well-known beaches, namely the Thousand Islands which consists of a cluster of small islands such as Pramuka Island, Tidung Island, Bidadari Island, and several other islands. To get to the Thousand Islands, you can take a speedboat from Marina Ancol Beach or from Muara Angke. Boat ticket counters are usually open from 6:30 a.m. with a ticket price of around IDR 50,000, or depending on the track. Once there, you can dive, play with sharks, or play adrenaline-pumping water rides.</string>
    <string name="Titlesub10_2">Kota Tua</string>
    <string name="Desc10_2">For those of you who want to experience the atmosphere of Jakarta in the past, you must visit the Kota Tua Jakarta area. Here are five museums that will enrich our insight into our history. The museums include: Wayang Museum, Fatahillah Museum, Bank Indonesia Museum, Bank Mandiri Museum, and Fine Arts Museum, which are open every Tuesday-Friday from 09.00-15.00 with an entrance ticket of IDR 2,000 for adults and IDR 600.00 for children. In addition, you can also explore the Old Town court using an ontel bicycle which can be rented for 30 minutes at a price of only Rp.10-15 thousand. Tired after traveling around the Old City? You can take a short break at the Batavia Cafe which serves a variety of traditional dishes. To get to Kota Tua, you can take the KRL and stop at Jakarta Kota Station then continue the journey on foot.</string>
    <string name="Titlesub10_3">Ancol</string>
    <string name="Desc10_3">This tourist spot in Jakarta is definitely familiar. Here there are various entertainment venues, such as Dunia Fantasi, Sea World, Ancol Beach, Ocean Dream Samudera, Atlantis, and Ancol Art Market. Taman Impian Jaya Ancol is open every day from 10.00-18.00. Around this tourist spot, there are also many restaurants serving seafood with beach views, such as Bandar Djakarta, which will spoil your eyes and tongue after a day of sightseeing.</string>
    <string name="Titlesub10_4">Kerak Telor</string>
    <string name="Desc10_4">The egg crust has a savory and sticky taste and is indeed a favorite for Jakartans. This typical Betawi dish is made from food ingredients such as white glutinous rice, chicken or duck eggs, dry roasted dried shrimp until it becomes serundeng, then added with fried onions, then given fine spices such as roasted coconut and others. The unique thing about this typical Betawi culinary is how to cook it. The egg is cooked when it is half cooked will be turned over the pan facing the hot charcoal from the brazier then left like that until it is cooked so that it becomes a crust.</string>
    <string name="labelprofile">Profile</string>
    <string name="labelname">Name</string>
</resources>